ONE MONTH AGO
[bell dinging]
KANYARAK BOONSI BORN 1988.09.25
DIED 2017.12.17
[Pasin, in Thai]
Why are you eating only that?
You should eat everything!
Mom is watching everything.
Hm!
You're the same, Dad.
You should eat everything.
Dad, let's stop listening to this song.
I'm sick of it.
Why? I want to listen to it.
-Let's listen to Lisa.
-K-pop?
Lisa is not K-pop. Now she's a world star.
You listen to her every day at home too.
Aren't you sick of it?
I'm more sick of your song.
You want to get off?
[Pasin] Long time no see!
[♪ bright upbeat music from radio]
Lisa followed me around every day
when I was in Korea.
[Pasin's son] Oh! You're lying again.
You're such a liar!
You want me to call her?
Yeah, call her. I said, call her.
Call her now. Yeah, call her.
[vehicles approaching]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[♪ intense action music playing]
[both grunting]
[thuds]
[mercenary] Go! Go! Go!
[♪ intense action music continues]
[thuds]
[in English] Hey, we need to borrow
your dad for a bit.
[Pasin's son breathing shakily]
[in Thai] It's okay.
Don't be scared, Atti.
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
EPISODE 06
THE TROJAN HORSE
[announcer, in English]
Three-nine, two-zero, five-zero,
seven-seven, three-four…
[Jinman] K.
[♪ tense music playing]
STYLE
::cue()
WILL ARRIVE AT 11:00 AM LOCAL TIME
IN THAILAND, CONTACT PASIN.
REQUEST ATTI'S LOCATION AND
THE KIDNAPPERS' INFORMATION BY 11:00
[sighs] This is how the mole e-mails.
When I'm in Thailand,
I'll be communicating
with the mole like this,
so verify the information.
[Jinwoo] That wasn't easy.
But it came out nicely.
Passport and satellite phone.
REPUBLIC OF KOREA PASSPORT
CHOI, MYUNG GYU
What's this? You're going in alone?
You're not going to take Jinwoo
or Cheolseung in there?
Hey, it's Pasin.
The two of us together will be fine.
I just…
Think about it, Jeong Jian.
We made our deal already,
but they still went ahead
and grabbed his son.
That means Babylon's planning
something else.
If the shopping mall's unguarded
while we're away,
they might use that opening to attack.
We need to leave some of you behind.
[satellite phone beeps]
[Cheolseung] This satellite phone
doesn't have a delay, does it?
[Jinwoo] No, it works right away.
Only on this channel.
[♪ tense music continues]
Are you sure about going alone like this?
[sighs] Don't you think it's safer
if I tagged along?
No, stay here.
Jian's going to need you more with her.
[engine revving]
[sighs softly]
[Jinman] Listen up, Jeong Jian.
There could be a situation
where you lose an arm.
What happens then?
Don't try to recover the arm you lost.
You should protect the one you still have.
[♪ tense music continues]
[engine starting, revving]
[♪ low pensive music playing]
[Pasin] Khao Lak Center,
locker number eight.
Password is 2-4-5-1.
You can find a device inside.
The coordinates will take you
to an Internet café.
I'll meet you there.
[♪ tense music playing]
[phone clattering]
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ music fades]
[indistinct chatter]
[in Thai] Pay later. Sit.
You can use the seat over there.
-[Jinman] There?
-Yeah.
Hey! Why are you cheating?
[gamer] What cheating? You crazy bastard.
[indistinct chatter continues]
[drone buzzing]
[♪ low tense music playing]
[patrons complaining indistinctly]
[blade scraping]
[attackers grunting]
[screams]
[♪ low suspenseful music playing]
[attackers yelping]
It's just him anyway.
Get him!
[attackers screaming]
[Pasin panting]
[groans]
[glass shatters]
[♪ tense music playing]
[taser zapping]
-[taser zapping]
-[groans softly]
[mercenary whistling]
[in English] Whoa… Two of them.
Still holding out.
Really haven't changed at all,
have you, Jinman?
[bat thudding]
[alarm beeping softly]
Huh?
[gasps]
[♪ lingering ominous music playing]
[Jin] Did you really think
that Babylon couldn't find you?
-[blows thudding]
-[Pasin groaning]
STYLE
::cue()
[Jin] I really do hate it.
The smell of blood.
[sniffs, groans in disgust]
The smell of sweat.
[roars angrily]
I'll break your neck!
Family… is always the problem.
You know, in the past,
they used to exterminate three generations
just to prevent
any uncertain future revenge.
Seems quite reasonable
when you think about it.
But it's really too bad.
People can't do that anymore.
Where's Atti?
[in Thai] You bitch!
[shushing]
[Pasin groans]
[in English] Turns out your son
has leukemia.
[Pasin grunts]
[Jin] It's really remarkable.
You poured all the money you made
for a decade into your son.
[grunts]
[spits]
[Pasin] Babylon!
You listen now.
Anything happens to Atti…
you all die.
Do not waste your time
thinking about killing me.
You should be thinking
about saving your son.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[gun cocking]
[gunshot ringing]
-[groans]
-[K] Good work.
[Jin] Don't worry.
We're taking good care of him.
So in return…
you are going to have to do
a little work for us.
[groans]
[howls in pain]
[Pasin] Atti.
So you're saying…
you never met my uncle there, then?
[♪ pensive music playing]
-[staple gun clicking]
-[Pasin groans]
Ah. Ah.
-[K] Can you hear me?
-I hear you.
Loud and clear.
We are listening to everything you say.
[Jin] Don't try anything fucking stupid.
If you do, your Atti won't be safe.
About 12 hours ago,
Jinman showed me the messages
that he got from the mole.
[♪ pensive music playing]
[Pasin] Once I got into Korea,
I went to that address
and got ambushed.
Pasin?
-[Pasin groans]
-[Brother chuckles softly]
[Jian] My uncle goes missing in Thailand,
and Master Pasin gets ambushed here.
And the two of them never even met up.
What about the message master received,
is it legit?
There are only a few people
who know the random combinations
and to change the e-mail every 12 hours.
Captain Jinman, the mole,
and then just us.
And unless someone in here leaked it,
there's no way the information
we're getting is compromised.
[sighs] Why can't I get in touch
with my uncle, then?
STYLE
::cue()
[♪ tense music playing]
Huh? What's up? You all right?
You should rest longer.
This won't kill me.
You just scan your hand here?
Ah. Wanna go up there?
Officer Jinwoo,
you're still working at the station?
Actually, I quit the police for now.
[chuckles]
You should just stay there.
It suits you better.
After being ambushed by Babylon,
seems like a bitter fit for me here.
And I should stay where I'm needed,
don't you think?
I was just… wasting away.
A police station out in the sticks?
Nothing happens out there.
[♪ tense music continues]
This was actually a grain dryer.
Brother turned it into an elevator.
[Jinwoo] That little punk keeps evolving
down in the basement.
You wouldn't believe what we went through.
It was hell getting this place
up and running.
Code Reds and Code Yellows
really helped us out.
Couldn't have done it without them.
We open the doors at 10:00
and close at 1900.
And then everyone goes home.
Quiet, not a single person's here.
It's perfect for what we're doing.
[Pasin] Everyone here,
are they all civilians?
It covers for us, for sure.
No one would suspect it.
[visitor] President Park!
-Hi, President Choi. How are you?
-Could you come over here?
[Jinwoo] Hey, I'm the president.
I'll be back.
President Choi,
you're coming by so early again.
You're killing me here, really!
[staff] I'll look at it later.
I'll look at it later.
No, no, no.
I'll look at it later, all right?
Oh?
[in Thai] Are you Thai? Eat some of this.
It's not as good as the one back home,
but we can eat it well enough.
I'm fine.
Pasin, why are you standing there
like an idiot?
Take this and go to the toilet.
Babylon is watching everything.
If you want to keep Atti alive,
don't try any funny business. Take it.
[in English] Thanks for everything, man.
[♪ music warping]
[faucet running]
You take a shit?
Why'd you disappear like that?
Don't worry too much about Atti.
Nothing's gonna happen.
Make a full recovery first.
Then you can find him.
[♪ tense pensive music playing]
STYLE
::cue()
Master! Are you feeling better?
-Anything on Jinman?
-No. Not yet.
How about the mole? Anything?
[♪ ominous music playing]
[Brother] Want to go down
to the shopping mall?
Unlike going to the outside,
you need one other thing to get in there.
[machine beeping]
The shopping mall has gotten twice as big.
That also means twice as much work,
but Jinwoo and Jeong Jian help out a lot.
Here I don't even have
to drive a forklift.
If something goes wrong,
is there an escape route?
Of course there is.
But the location is a secret
that only the security manager knows.
Because until recently,
a fake murthehelp app was out there.
The… the dumbass with the stutter is…
that one, isn't he?
[Brother] We lost a lot of clients
because of them,
but we got a lot of them back now.
[♪ tense pensive music playing]
Oh.
Check this out.
Jeong Jian. [chuckles]
Uh… My butt gets sweaty
so she got this for me.
It feels cool. It's nice and dry.
Murthehelp looks like a tight operation
that's so thorough,
then you see things like this.
[Brother] She even bought me two,
in case I need one later.
It's just a gaggle of freaks
that are in there.
[Brother] But she still treats me
like a kid.
[Jin] Is this stuttering fool
really the brains?
Should I just kill him?
[sighs]
How many times do I have to tell you?
Don't you know how to knock?
Oh, I did.
I just didn't hear an answer, so I…
I'll make sure
that I knock louder next time, miss.
Why are you here?
Uh, I'm here about the bus explosion.
Shouldn't we investigate it?
I was looking over the victims'
families' insurance claims
and I started thinking…
it could've been an attack on us
from Jeong Jinman's side.
In that case,
I think we should make preparations.
We should have some contingencies.
Things like this shouldn't happen here,
isn't that right?
Babylon's image is at risk, and it's just,
the employees are feeling really anxious.
The audit team is still investigating, no?
[Inseop] Yes, well, that's true, but…
Then let's just wait a bit longer.
Preparedness is a constant state.
I just think there's too much delay in…
Uh… Never mind, yeah.
Okay. Should I leave?
Should we take care of that idiot lawyer?
He believes that Jeong Jinman was
the one who attacked us.
I wouldn't worry about it.
[scoffs] I guess.
That lawyer's brain couldn't even
comprehend what went on.
That the reason the bus exploded
that night…
[chuckles] …was to cover up
Bale killing Jun.
STYLE
::cue()
Pasin, when we find Atti
and when President Jinman comes back,
can't we all live here together again?
I think it would be… would be nice.
[scoffs]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[Jinman panting]
[mercenary] Mr. Jeong Jinman!
Thanks to you, Mr. Jinman,
Kuma and my team were taken out,
and I got transferred here…
where it's hot as hell.
Ah…
Jo Seonggu, the team leader.
Oh… Thought you forgot.
Well, shoot…
So tell me, Jinman,
why'd you wage a damn war
with Babylon and start this shit?
[groans] Babylon struck first.
I didn't start it.
Makes no difference who started it…
you don't just jump into a battle
you have no chance of winning.
You know, you should've just gone
with the flow. Just like a tree.
If the wind starts blowing,
then you should sway.
Otherwise, you end up taking
the damn beating.
Yeah?
Or else, you'll find yourself like this.
Understand?
-Jo Seonggu.
-What?
Just shut up.
Tell me where Atti is now, I'm in a rush.
Then… I won't kill you
for old times' sake.
Oh, fuck me.
I was about to shit my pants and tell you.
[sighs]
Hey, Jeong Jinman…
you have no idea
what's going on right now, do you?
Just wait a little bit.
I will show you exactly what will happen
to your precious niece and murthehelp.
It's all about to go down.
I hope you're not in pain yet.
Uh-huh. 'Cause from here on,
there's gonna be a lot.
[Seonggu grunts]
[blows thudding]
[Jian] Are we sure they're keeping
Pasin's son in that van?
We never got a picture.
Then that would mean
the mole gave us some false information.
[Pasin] I'll go and handle it.
You need to recover,
you shouldn't go anywhere.
We don't even know if it's accurate.
I have to confirm it. I have to go there.
You guys should… find Jinman quickly.
You should hurry.
If it's to confirm it,
-I think I should go instead.
-Eonni.
[Cheolseung] I don't think
any of us should leave.
It's not a good idea, especially
with the captain missing right now.
Wouldn't it be better to just recruit
a few Code Reds instead?
No.
At the negotiations, they helped us,
but we can't assume
they're on our side yet.
It's too dangerous.
If we move too quickly
and they find out we don't have Jinman,
-they might betray us.
-We're out of time now.
Wait!
The rest of us will hold
the fort down here.
Minhye Eonni can go with Master,
couldn't you?
I think it's too dangerous
to move alone right now.
[K] The shopping mall
is on basement level 2.
STYLE
::cue()
They installed cameras operating with
motion sensors throughout the whole area.
If an intruder is detected,
the alarm goes off
and the entire security system activates.
[Jin] He's one crafty bastard.
He knows how we prefer
to keep our operations covert.
He knows that public exposure
would derail our missions.
That's why he built the shopping mall
beneath a site
that's completely full of civilians.
Is this the only exit?
There's no other way out?
That's the only one that we could find.
[Jin] Once our Thai friend does his job
and eliminates So Minhye,
the shopping mall will be ours.
And they'll be defenseless
except for their internal security system.
And Jeong Jinman's where?
Do we know where he is?
Thailand.
We got confirmation of his entry.
We're currently tracking him down
with help from the Thai branch.
[♪ tense plotting music playing]
Once you have Jeong Jian,
that bastard will have no other choice.
Jeong Jinman will come for her.
It's only a matter of time.
-Is it just the four of us going?
-[Jin] No.
Considering our previous attempt…
for this mission,
I will be assigning two teams.
Are you not gonna tell Q
that we already caught Jeong Jinman?
Don't say anything until we catch her.
We need Q to believe
that Jeong Jinman killed J.
She'll put everything
into capturing Jeong Jian. Pow.
[pants and gasps]
[strained grunt]
[groans in pained effort]
[labored panting]
[grunts, pants]
[clanging]
[in Thai] Fuck! Damn!
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[distant rapid gunfire]
[guns cock]
[gunfire]
[in English] Go.
[gunman groaning, screaming]
-[knife slashing]
-[screaming stops]
[Seonggu clicks tongue]
[gunfire]
[Seonggu groans]
[♪ suspenseful music continues]
[screams in pain]
Where are you holding Atti?
I ain't saying shit to you,
you dumb mother--
[Seonggu screams in pain]
You can't kill me, I said where--
STYLE
::cue()
[birds screeching]
[♪ tense music playing]
[♪ music fades]
[Pasin] That's where they're holding Atti.
[sighs]
So from here, I'll go on foot.
I'll circle to the back and fire a shot
to draw them in.
After the shot, wait one minute.
Then you hit them from the side
and start the rescue.
Pasin…
I swear, I'll rescue Atti.
[Pasin] Yeah.
Minhye…
thank you for everything.
[phone buzzing]
JIAN - I'M UNEASY ABOUT NOT BEING ABLE
TO REACH MY UNCLE.
YOU BE CAREFUL TOO, MINHYE.
[truck engine revving]
[crashing]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[grunts]
[tires screeching]
[grunting, panting]
-[gunshots]
-[glass shatters]
[gasps]
[gunshots]
[groans]
[Minhye grunting]
STYLE
::cue()
[Minhye] Pasin…
[gunshots]
[♪ lingering tense music playing]
[line ringing]
I took care of Minhye.
Now… I'll go to the shopping mall.
[♪ music fades]
[lock clanging]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[guns cock]
I hired three black-hat hackers
and secured the e-mails exchanged
between Jeong Jinman and his informant.
-[Jin] Do they have what it takes?
-[announcer] Seven, seven.
[K] Yes. They even hacked the NIS before.
[announcer] One-one-zero, one-zero-six…
nine-three, five-zero,
six-nine…
[phone buzzing]
Speak.
Jeong Jinman left?
[yells] Fuck!
[panting]
Tell our Thai branch we need everyone
to prioritize capturing Jeong Jinman.
Q needs to start the mission right away.
We're out of time now.
Tick-tock.
Right away.
[sighs]
-Should I go alone?
-You go ahead.
I'm gonna eat first.
STYLE
::cue()
Jian! Jinman's location was sent to us!
You know how, right? The name
and the passport number all match.
You sure
this is actually the mole's message?
Hey, I thought I told you earlier,
only we know the mole's method to…
Look at this.
These are the e-mails the mole sent
my uncle over the past year.
At the end of every subject line…
they put this here.
I think the mole hid it. Now look.
[♪ tense pensive music playing]
They stop here.
[exhales heavily]
It was right in front of us
this whole time.
The last one with the mark was sent
a week ago.
Babylon assholes somehow intercepted it.
Pasin?
What happened? Did you find Atti?
Where is Minhye?
[Jinwoo grunting]
[rhythmic tapping]
[♪ tense music playing]
BABYLON KIDNAPPED PASIN.
POSSIBLE PASIN IS NOW A DOUBLE AGENT.
[Cheolseung] Thai comrade…
what's going on, man?
Are you doing all right?
Where's Minhye?
Master, please tell me.
What'd you do with my uncle and Minhye?
-Jian, get out of here.
-Master!
[Jian groans]
Get the hell out of here!
[Cheolseung groans]
[Jian groans]
[♪ intense suspenseful music playing]
[screams]
-[Cheolseung yells]
-[grunting]
[Jian panting]
[both grunting]
[groans]
[grunts]
[♪ intense suspenseful music continues]
[both grunting]
[groans]
[Cheolseung yells]
[♪ music ends]
[device beeps]
[computer beeping]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[panting]
STYLE
::cue()
What?
[error beeping]
[slams lock]
[Brother] What's…?
[grunts in frustration]
[♪ suspenseful music continues]
Jinwoo?
Cheolseung?
Jeong Jian, where are you?
Pasin's turned on us. We have to go!
What did you say?
There's no time.
I'll explain later. We have to go!
[♪ suspenseful music continues]
Pasin, what are you doing?
[screams] Damn it, Master, what the hell?
Jian…
once you pull out your gun,
you just shoot it, all right?
[Jian yelps, groans]
-Brother! Brother! Brother!
-[Brother groans]
[Jian] Pasin!
Please, what are you doing? Please!
[♪ menacing music playing]
[Jin] Watch carefully.
First, the king,
we separate him from the amateur queen.
Then we take their knight
and turn him into ours, just like this.
And send him in like a Trojan horse.
As for the bishops and pawns
who lost their knight,
just steamroll the whole lot.
[beeping]
Both of the units have been docked.
Initiating the hack.
Thanks for working hard.
[in Japanese] What's the situation?
[in English] We've taken control
of their entire security system now.
We only need to move in.
[in Japanese] Tell Q to eliminate Pasin
once Jeong Jian is captured.
[in English] Then, we go in there…
and capture the queen.
[♪ menacing music continues]
Q, driven by pure revenge,
will capture Jeong Jian.
And once we've taken the queen…
the king is put in endgame.
A SHOP FOR KILLERS 2
[♪ music ends]
[Jin] Korean barbecue?
[groans] The smell's gonna stick.
[exhales]
Oh, wow. [chuckles]
I always wanted to meet you in person.
I know it looks shabby, but…
Our meat here is out of this world.
So that's why I invited you.
Hm?
[♪ tense pensive music playing]
Ahn Seongbeom.
It's a pleasure.
[♪ closing theme music playing]
BASED ON THE NOVEL BY KANG JI YOUNG